Get ready for the race of your life.
Driven is a action, drama film directed by Renny Harlin.
Talented rookie race-car driver Jimmy Bly has started losing his
focus and begins to slip in the race rankings.
It's no wonder, with the immense pressure being shoveled on him by his overly ambitious
promoter brother as well as Bly's romance with his arch rival's girlfriend Sophia.
With much riding on Bly, car owner Carl Henry brings former
racing star Joe Tanto on board to help Bly.
To drive Bly back to the top of the rankings, Tanto must first deal with the emotional
scars left over from a tragic racing accident which nearly took his life.
Joe Tanto, played by Sylvester Stallone.
Carl Henry, played by Burt Reynolds.
Jimmy Bly, played by Kip Pardue.
Lucretia Clan, played by Stacy Edwards.
Beau Brandenburg, played by Til Schweiger.
Cathy Heguy, played by Gina Gershon.
Driven is a 2001 American sports action film directed by Renny Harlin and
starring Sylvester Stallone, who also wrote and produced.
The film centers on a young racing driver's effort to win the CART
FedEx Championship Series auto racing championship.
Prior to production, Stallone was seen at many Formula One races, but he was unable to procure enough information about the category due to the
secrecy with which teams protect their cars, so he decided to base the film on the Championship Auto Racing Teams (CART) racing series.
Released on April 27, 2001 by Warner Bros.
Pictures, Driven received generally negative reviews from
critics, and was a commercial failure.
Stallone includes "Driven" in his list of movies he has regretted making.
The film explores themes of career, sports, competition, automobile.
The tone is emotional.